{
    "id": "5d53b5d600e1477b90e78148d5e5602e",
    "title": "Adjectives And Adverbs",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The fish tasted …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "awful",
                "awfully"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c458b5feaf044b98a6fbadba45b17292"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is …………………. cold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bitter",
                "bitterly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8c84f00cb8ef493fa857af95bf0fed3f"
        },
        {
            "question": "This novel is …………………. interesting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8ad55370f49249b28814277cc80a0df1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am ………………… glad to meet you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a2f5d10fbbbc4389aa85edfa5e1110e9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I could not find it ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "anywhere",
                "nowhere"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b8a5ab50be7d407aad9e1092167ec39e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The child ate the sweets …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "greedy",
                "greedily"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dbe8549685574fc3ab550a759578746c"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will pay …………………. for your mistakes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "dear",
                "dearly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4f68d382b8954c999479c930abf1c4d1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know ………………….. about him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "anything",
                "nothing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dc5bdb81d7ba480b9a8a42f3053aeb5c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t got ………………… money.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "no"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "84a7fd40512f4ae484ca97031d6f366f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was driving …………………. fast.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unusual",
                "unusually"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cd90d11901644eaca875f66ad6cebdab"
        }
    ]
}